{
  "chapter": 16,
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "In which type of cloud service consumers have most of the security responsibilities?",
      "incorrect_answers": ["IaaS", "PaaS", "SaaS", "Same in all of these"],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is done through Identity management?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Preventing unauthorized use",
        "controlling access to data in the cloud",
        "Maintaining user roles",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Which document works as the reference for both the service provider and consumer in case of any security dispute in cloud?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Project agreement document",
        "Service level agreement",
        "Security agreement document",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "By running over which application, the PaaS consumers can access the abstraction layer?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Using APIs",
        "Using direct calls",
        "Using programs",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "From consumer’s end, who must review the SLA document before making the final agreement?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Legal expert",
        "Business expert",
        "Technical expert",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who among the following from enterprise’s behalf must review the SLA document to ensure security in cloud?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Legal expert",
        "Business expert",
        "Technical expert",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Security management responsibilities of SaaS application consumers include managing of",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Application security management",
        "Platform security management",
        "Operational security management",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Security management responsibilities of PaaS application consumers include managing of",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Application security management",
        "Operational security management",
        "Platform security management",
        "Both a and b"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Covert channel problem is a threat to",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Information confidentiality",
        "Integrity of information",
        "Information availability",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Identification and access management plays the vital roles in cloud computing as",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Anyone can work in cloud.",
        "Consumers work outside trusted network boundary.",
        "Virtualization brings the vulnerability.",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Tell the statement if True or False. ‘In federated identity system, the user credentials are stored in one application only.’",
      "incorrect_answers": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": 1
    }
  ]
}
